Witness the bloody origin.
The King's Man is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by Matthew Vaughn.
As a collection of history's worst tyrants and criminal masterminds gather to plot a
war to wipe out millions, one man must race against time to stop them.
Orlando Oxford, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Polly, played by Gemma Arterton.
Grigori Rasputin, played by Rhys Ifans.
Morton, played by Matthew Goode.
King George / Kaiser Wilhelm / Tsar Nicholas, played by Tom Hollander.
Conrad Oxford, played by Harris Dickinson.
The King's Man is a 2021 British spy action film directed by Matthew Vaughn
from his story and a screenplay he wrote with Karl Gajdusek.
The third installment in the British Kingsman film series, which is based on the comic book The Secret Service (later retitled Kingsman) by Mark Millar and Dave
Gibbons, in turn based on a concept by Millar and Vaughn, it is a prequel to Kingsman: The Secret Service (2014) and Kingsman: The Golden Circle (2017).
Its ensemble cast includes Ralph Fiennes (also one of its executive producers), Gemma Arterton, Rhys Ifans,
Matthew Goode, Tom Hollander, Harris Dickinson, Daniel Brühl, Djimon Hounsou, and Charles Dance.
It focuses on several events during World War I and
the birth of the Kingsman organization.
It was released in the United States on 22 December 2021, and in the United Kingdom on 26 December 2021 by
20th Century Studios following several release delays partially due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $126 million against
nearly a $100 million budget, making it a box-office bomb.
The film explores themes of london, england, world
war i, spy, based on comic, prequel.
The tone is intense.